Guide to the George A. Romero Archival Collection, 1962-2017 SC.2019.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Scripts, circa 1964-2017; I.
  - Produced Works, 1967-2017; 1.
    - Monkey Shines, 1988; 12.
      - Monkey Shines final draft (copy 4), May 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Monkey Shines final draft (copy 5), May 1987 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Monkey Shines final draft (copy 6), May 1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Monkey Shines final draft (copy 7), May 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Monkey Shines reading script final draft, May 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Monkey Shines shooting script final draft, June 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Monkey Shines shooting script final draft ("George" written across cover page, includes notes and diagrams laid in), June 1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Monkey Shines shooting script final draft colored revision pages througout (Christine Forrest Romero's parts higlighted), June 1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Monkey Shines shooting script in Mylar sleeves with highlighting/annotation, 1987 (Box 22, Item 2)
    - Tales from the Darkside: The Movie, 1990; 13.
      An anthology horror film consisting of three stories of monsters and the grotesque. Filmed in and around Pittsburgh. One segment, "The Cat from Hell," was adapted by George A. Romero from a short story written by Stephen King. It was originally included in early draft scripts for Creepshow 2. Starring Debbie Harry, Steve Buscemi, Julianne Moore, Christian Slater, David Johansen, and James Remar. Written by George A. Romero and Michael McDowell and directed by John Harrison.
      - Tales from the Darkside: The Movie script, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Two Evil Eyes ["The Facts in the Case of M. Valdemar"], 1990; 14.
      An anthology horror film consisting of two adaptations of stories written by Edgar Allen Poe. Filmed in Pittsburgh. The two segments are "The Facts in the Case of M. Valdemar," written and directed by George A. Romero and starring Adrienne Barbeau, and "The Black Cat," written by Dario Argento and Franco Ferrini, directed by Argento, and starring Harvey Keitel.
      - "The Facts in the Case of M. Valdemar" draft (59 pages), undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - "The Facts in the Case of M. Valdemar" first draft (62 pages), February 1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - "The Facts in the Case of M. Valdemar" 2 copies together with "April" on envelope, February 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - "The Facts in the Case of M. Valdemar" second draft (58 pages), May 1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Night of the Living Dead, 1990; 15.
      A remake of George A. Romero's debut feature, in which a small group of people attempt to survive in a remote farmhouse as the dead rise to feed on the living. Filmed in Evans City, PA. Starring Tony Todd, Patricia Tallman, Tom Towles, and Bill Moseley. Written by George A. Romero and directed by Tom Savini.
      - Night of the Living Dead, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
        Envelope notes "Scenes from childhood/kindergarten"
      - Night of the Living Dead first draft (copy 1), February 1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Night of the Living Dead first draft (copy 2), February 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Night of the Living Dead first draft (copy 3), February 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Night of the Living Dead first draft (copy 4), February 1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Night of the Living Dead first draft (copy 5), February 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Night of the Living Dead first draft (copy 6), February 1989 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - The Dark Half, 1993; 16.
      A horror film about an author whose alter ego comes to life and terrorizes those closest to him. Filmed in Southwestern Pennsylvania. Starring Timothy Hutton, Amy Madigan, and Michael Rooker. Based on a book by Stephen King. Written and directed by George A. Romero.
      - The Dark Half noted "Old Very First Draft before edit of draft 1", undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - The Dark Half first draft, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - The Dark Half noted "Pre-2nd draft edit copy and Orion notes", June 1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - The Dark Half second draft, June 1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - The Dark Half third draft (copy 1), August 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - The Dark Half third draft (copy 2), August 1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - The Dark Half fourth draft, August 25, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - The Dark Half fifth draft (with revision pages laid in), October 6, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - The Dark Half script, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - The Dark Half script, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - The Dark Half script, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Jacaranda Joe, 1994-1995; 17.
      A short film set at a sensationalist talk show in which the host explores the sightings of a monstrous creature in Florida with a series of guests. Filmed at Valencia Community College in Florida with a cast and crew mixing local professionals and student filmmakers. Written and directed by George A. Romero.
      - Jacaranda Joe script, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Iron City Asskickers [Untitled George Romero Wrestling Project] by J.B. Destiny, 1998; 18.
      The pilot episode for a proposed TV series about passionate rivalries amongst wrestlers in Pittsburgh. Written by and starring J.B. Destiny and directed by George A. Romero.
      - Iron City Asskickers [Untitled George Romero Wrestling Project] script by J.B. Destiny, includes memo regarding other projects and dated, May 14, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Bruiser, 2000; 19.
      A drama about a man for whom the cruelty of those around him drives him to violence after he wakes up to find his face replaced by a blank mask. Filmed in Toronto. Starring Jason Flemyng, Peter Stormare, and Leslie Hope. Written and directed by George A. Romero.
      - Bruiser first draft, October 1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Bruiser noted "Old Script" on cover, character list laid in, March 1998 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Bruiser third draft, April 21, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Bruiser script (pages 73-83 attached at back), June 19, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Bruiser script (copy 1), September 16, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Bruiser script (with cover page depicting masks) (copy 2), September 16, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Bruiser script (copy 3), September 16, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Bruiser script (copy 1), April 14, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Bruiser script (copy 2), April 14, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Bruiser revised script, June 16, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Bruiser shooting script colored page revisions, July 26, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Bruiser script, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Land of the Dead [Dead Reckoning], 2005; 20.
      A sequel to George A. Romero's original "Dead" trilogy, made more than 20 years after Day of the Dead, in which humanity has settled into a highly stratified classist and racist society within a small, fortified section of downtown Pittsburgh. Known as Dead Reckoning in early screenplays. Filmed in Toronto. Starring Simon Baker, Dennis Hopper, John Leguizamo, and Asia Argento. Written and directed by George A. Romero.
      - Land of the Dead [Dead Reckoning] first draft (copy 1), July 25, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Land of the Dead [Dead Reckoning] first draft (copy 2), July 25, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Land of the Dead [Dead Reckoning] revised draft, August 16, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Land of the Dead [Dead Reckoning] script, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Land of the Dead [Dead Reckoning] script, October 3, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Land of the Dead script, January 9, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Land of the Dead script (copy 1), July 13, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Land of the Dead script (copy 2), July 13, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Land of the Dead script (incomplete copy 1), July 13, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Land of the Dead script (incomplete copy 2), July 14, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Land of the Dead "Final Draft 7 Demo" watermark, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Land of the Dead shooting script with colored revision sheets dated variously, October 3 - December 8, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Land of the Dead bound presentation copy signed by cast, October 3, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Land of the Dead revised script signed by cast, November 23, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Diary of the Dead, 2007; 21.
      A horror film re-imagining the initial moment in which the dead rise, set among a group of University of Pittsburgh film students. An adaptation of a 2004 script by George A. Romero for the pilot of a Night of the Living Dead television series. Filmed in Ontario. Starring Michelle Morgan. Written and directed by Romero.
      - Diary of the Dead script, September 12, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Diary of the Dead full blue revision script (copy 1), October 9, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Diary of the Dead blue revision script (copy 2), October 9, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Diary of the Dead blue revision script (copy 3), October 9, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Diary of the Dead blue revision script (incomplete), October 9, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Diary of the Dead script (incomplete), 2006 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Diary of the Dead script (arranged in reverse order), undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Diary of the Dead script, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Survival of the Dead [Blank of the Dead], 2009; 22.
      A horror film continuing the re-telling of the zombie story begun in Diary of the Dead, in which survivors make it to a remote island on which old rivalries threaten the safety of the inhabitants. Filmed in Ontario. Referred to during development as Blank of the Dead. Starring Kathleen Munroe, Alan van Sprang, and Kenneth Welsh. Written and directed by George A. Romero.
      - Survival of the Dead [Blank of the Dead] June 2006 script with revision pages from Sept and Oct 2008, June-Oct 2008 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - The Little World of Humongo Dongo [Le Petit Monde d'Humongo Dongo] [The Little World of Humongo Bongo], Belgian edition 1996, US edition 2018; 23.
      A children's book about fantastical creatures trying to coexist despite their differences while also learning about their impact on the ecology and environment of their planet. Written and illustrated by Romero in English, the book was originally published in Belgium in a French translation as Le Petit Monde d'Humongo Dongo. It was later republished in 2018 with the original English text with the name changed to The Little World of Humongo Bongo.
      - The Little World of Humongo Dongo draft text and illustration layout, noted as "Original", November 1994 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - The Little World of Humongo Dongo draft manuscript (3 copies), undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - The Little World of Humongo Dongo draft manuscript with note "No, it's not about Harry Riems", undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - The Little World of Humongo Dongo draft manuscript with note about double entendre in name, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - The Little World of Humongo Dongo draft manuscript (copy 1), undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - The Little World of Humongo Dongo draft manuscript (copy 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - The Little World of Humongo Dongo draft manuscript note for new version to be published in English, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - The Little World of Humongo Dongo draft for English edition with proof illustrations including French text, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - The Little World of Humongo Dongo reduced size publisher galleys, November 1994 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - The Little World of Humongo Dongo oversize original artwork maquettes and page layouts, undated (Oversize 23)
      - The Little World of Humongo Bongo draft manuscript (2 copies), undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
        Text for new English edition with title and character name change from "Humongo Dongo" to "Humongo Bongo."
    - The Liberator, 2017; 24.
      A book produced for a gallery show featuring etchings by artist George Nama and a short story about a golem written by George A. Romero. From a gallery show at Shepherd /W&K Galleries and Jack Rutberg Fine Arts Inc in 2017.
      - The Liberator manuscript (7 pages), undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - The Liberator manuscript (13 pages) (2 copies), undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Unproduced Works, circa 1964-2013; 2.
    Materials in unproduced works include treatments, drafts, shooting scripts, and manuscripts related to unproduced or unpublished works in film, television, and literature. All items are scripts unless otherwise noted. All working titles or alternate titles are noted in [brackets]. Many items are unattributed and are assumed to be written by Romero unless otherwise noted.
    - Abominable Snowman, 1993-1995; 1.
      - Abominable Snowman treatment by Ilya Salkind, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Abominable Snowman screenplay by Philip Poe, story by Ilya Salkind and Philip Poe, revised draft, June 23, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Angel 7, January 1996; 2.
      - Angel 7 treatment for teleplay first draft, January 1996 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Animal Hour, December 8, 1992; 3.
      - Animal Hour partial treatment, includes letter to Demi Moore about project, December 8, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Apartment Living, circa 1988; 4.
      - Apartment Living treatment by George A. Romero and Joseph Stillman, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Apartment Living treatment (2 copies), undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Apartment Living treatment by George A. Romero, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Apartment Living by Warren Hitte, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Apartment Living by George A. Romero and Joseph Stillman, April 13, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Apartment Living by George A. Romero and Joseph Stillman, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - The Assassination, circa 2001; 5.
      - The Assassination by Michael January, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - The Assassination by Michael January, revised by George A. Romero, February 17, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - The Assassination script (121 pages), undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - The Assassination script (129 pages), undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - The Assassination script (135 pages), undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Before I Wake, circa 1994-1995; 6.
      - Before I Wake by Lucky Gold (119 pages) (copy 1), undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Before I Wake by Lucky Gold (119 pages) (copy 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Before I Wake by Lucky Gold (121 pages), undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Before I Wake first draft, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Before I Wake third draft, September 29, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Before I Wake third draft, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Before I Wake 2nd Fox Draft (copy 1), July 28, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Before I Wake 2nd Fox Draft (copy 2), July 28, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Before I Wake 2nd Fox Draft (copy 3), July 28, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Before I Wake 2nd Fox Draft (copy 4), July 28, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Before I Wake script, October 6, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Before I Wake script (copy 1), December 5, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Before I Wake script (copy 2), December 5, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - The Bell Witch, 1998; 7.
      - Bell Witch brief treatment (2 copies), undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Bell Witch treatment (42 pages), undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Bell Witch treatment (41 pages), undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Bell Witch treatment 1st draft (2 copies), September 8, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Bell Witch treatment (2 copies), undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Bell Witch first draft script, October 20, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Big Lazarus, circa 1987; 8.
      - Big Lazarus treatment by Dominic [sic] Muir on concept by George A. Romero, revised November 2, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 10)
        Title page credits the treatment to "Dominic Muir." This refers to Domonic Muir.
      - Big Lazarus treatment with note attributing authorship to Dominic [sic] Muir, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Big Lazarus treatment (includes letter about titles) (copy 1), undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Big Lazarus treatment (includes letter about titles) (copy 2), undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Big Lazarus treatment (includes letter about titles) (copy 3), undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Big Lazarus treatment, undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Black Gothic, undated; 9.
      - Black Gothic treatment or story, undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Black Mariah, circa 1993; 10.
      - Black Mariah rough draft by Preston A. Whitmore II and Jay Bonansinga, August 6, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Black Mariah first draft by Preston A. Whitmore II and Jay Bonansinga, September 14, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Black Mariah (incomplete draft), undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - The Calling, undated; 11.
      - The Calling, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Cartoon, undated; 12.
      - Cartoon, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Chain Letter, circa 1996-1997; 13.
      - Chain Letter by Gene Quintano, August 31, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Chain Letter screen treatment by George A. Romero, April 1997 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Chain Letter second draft, December 1997 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Chain Letter (includes 3.5 diskette), undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Chain Letter (incomplete draft), undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Chain Letter, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Cherubs, 1995-1996; 14.
      - Cherubs proposal for a TV series, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Cherubs first draft treatment (3 copies), February 1996 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - The Collaboration, circa 1999; 15.
      - The Collaboration by Jeff Monahan (copy 1), undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - The Collaboration by Jeff Monahan (copy 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - The Collaboration by George A. Romero and Jeff Monahan first draft, April 26, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - The Collaboration, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Copperhead Conquers the Warhawks, 1982-1984; 16.
      Numerous alternate titles were used for this project including "Laurel/Marvel Movie," Copperhead, and Mongrel: the Legend of Copperhead.
      - Copperhead Conquers the Warhawks [Laurel/Marvel Movie] expanded outline draft by Jim Shooter, December 9, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Copperhead Conquers the Warhawks [Copperhead] draft by Jim Shooter, July 20, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Copperhead Conquers the Warhawks [Copperhead] by George A. Romero second draft, October 1983 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Copperhead Conquers the Warhawks Condensed Version by George A. Romero and Jim Shooter, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Copperhead Conquers the Warhaws [Laurel/Marvel Project] extended treatment draft 2, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Copperhead Conquers the Warhawks by George A. Romero (copy 1), 1983 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Copperhead Conquers the Warhawks by George A. Romero (copy 2), 1983 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Copperhead Conquers the Warhawks by George A. Romero (copy 3), 1983 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Copperhead Conquers the Warhawks "Working Title" plot outline by Jim Shooter, January 27, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Copperhead Conquers the Warhawks [Mongrel: The Legend of Copperhead] storyoutline and comic panels by George A. Romero and Shooter, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Cryptid, 2001-2013; 17.
      - Cryptid first draft, May 19, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Cryptid 4th draft 2nd revision by Eren Cain, May 5, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Cupie, October 1996; 18.
      - Cupie treatment first draft, October 1996 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Cut Numbers, circa 1989; 19.
      - Cut Numbers script, name of source material author Nick Tosches written at top, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Cut Numbers first draft (copy 1), January 1989 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Cut Numbers first draft (copy 2), January 1989 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Cut Numbers first draft (copy 3), January 1989 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Cut Numbers first draft (copy 4), January 1989 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Dark Secrets, undated; 20.
      - Dark Secrets draft script, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Dark Young Things, undated; 21.
      - Dark Young Things by Tom DeVille based on The Ill by George A. Romero, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
        The Ill originally based on a screenplay by Hal Hartley.
    - Darque Passages, undated; 22.
      - Darque Passages treatment for TV series, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Dead Man's Catch, October 17, 1996; 23.
      - Dead Man's Catch 7 page treatment (3 copies) first draft, October 17, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Dead Man's Catch 8 page treatment (3 copies; 1 copy "For Peter"; 1 copy with note "Sent to Peter") first draft, October 17, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Death of Death, circa 1999; 24.
      - Death of Death chapter 1 and 2 of unfinished novel, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Death of Death early chapters of unfinished novel, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Death of Death first chapter of unfinished novel, June 1999 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Divine Spirit, undated; 25.
      - Divine Spirit treatment (5 copies), undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - The Dogs, April 30, 1974; 26.
      - The Dogs outline for a film by Mel and Ethel Brez, April 30, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Dracula, undated; 27.
      - Dracula teleplay page 38 revisions at end, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Dracula pages 4 and 5 missing, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Dracula, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Dreamwalker, October 16, 1996; 28.
      - Dreamwalker outline and treatment for TV series first draft, October 16, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Empire of the Dead VI, undated; 29.
      - Empire of the Dead VI treatment or story, undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Enemies, undated; 30.
      - Enemies [Untitled] treatment, undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
        Untitled story or treatment. Appears to be early draft of Enemies with similar storyline and characters.
      - Enemies treatment, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Figments, undated; 31.
      - Figments script, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Flying Horses, 1994-2004; 32.
      - Flying Horses first draft, February 1994 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Flying Horses second draft, February 1996 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Flying Horses revised, January 2, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Flying Horses (copy 1), undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Flying Horses (copy 2), undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - The Footage [Bigfoot], undated; 33.
      - The Footage [Bigfoot] original draft, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - The Footage [Bigfoot] treatment, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - The Footage [Bigfoot] "Franco Version", undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Friends, June 24, 1984; 34.
      - Friends by Lee Kalcheim revised draft (copy 1), June 24, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Friends by Lee Kalcheim revised draft (copy 2), June 24, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Funky Coven, undated; 35.
      - Funky Coven treatment (3 copies), undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Funky Coven script (copy 1), undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Funky Coven script (copy 2), undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - George Romero's Scary Tales, undated; 36.
      - George Romero's Scary Tales, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Germs, undated; 37.
      - Germs treatment, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Ghost Town, undated; 38.
      - Ghost Town script, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon, 1999-2005; 39.
      - The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon, circa 1999 (Box 35, Folder 1)